Panama
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Panama, 2.1.1.1.18
  - Captain Smith, chief officer and American flag on board United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, 1912 September 5-6; 13; 1359; 56; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Ruins of earthquake, Frank R. Roberson in foreground, Kingston, Jamaica, 1912; 14; 1360; 135; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Street scene, Kingston Jamaica, 1912; 15; 1361; 136; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - House of Assembly, Spanish Town, Jamaica, 1912; 16; 1362; 137; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Government house, Spanish Town, Jamaica, 1912; 17; 1363; 138; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Stream scene, Jamaica, 1912; 18; 1365; 140; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - House and palms, Rio Cobre, Jamaica, 1912; 19; 1366; 141; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Orchid path, Hope Gardens, Jamaica, 1912 September 6; 20; 1367; 71; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Hope Gardens, Jamaica, 1912 September 6; 21; 1368; 72; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Suburban home, Jamaica, 1912 September 6; 22; 1369; 74; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Arbor covered with bougainvillea, Hope Gardens, Jamaica, 1912; 23; 1370; 70; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Plantation huts, Frank R. Roberson in doorway, Jamaica, 1912; 24; 1371; 145; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Tree, Spanish Town, Jamaica, 1912; 25; 1373; 143; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Native girls, Jamaica, 1912 September 6; 26; 1375; 69; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Main road into Kingston Jamaica, banana plantation on either side of road, 1912 September 6; 27; 1376; 146; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Post office building, Kingston Jamaica, 1912 September 6; 28; 1377; 68; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Bougainvillea, Jamaica, 1912 September 6; 29; 1378; 58; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Hotel and lawn, Jamaica, 1912; 30; 1379; 57; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Road to Spanish Town, Frank R. Roberson sitting at base of tree, Jamaica, 1912 September 6; 31; 1380; 51; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - New Washington Hotel, Colón, 1912; 32; 1381; 133; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - English church, Colón, 1912; 33; 1382; 132; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  Box 1221
- Panama, 2.1.1.1.18
  - Boulevard, Second Street, Colón, 1912; 1; 1383; 131; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Fourth and Bolivar Streets, Colón, 1912; 2; 1384; 130; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Looking toward station, Colón, 1912; 3; 1385; 128; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Houses on waterfront, Colón, 1912; 4; 1386; 134; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Frank R. Roberson at ticket window, Colón, 1912; 5; 1387; 52; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Entering Cristobal from Colón, 1912; 6; 1388; 129; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Statue in front of Ferdinand de Lesseps’s house (Columbus), Cristobal, 1912; 7; 1389; 49; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Roosevelt Avenue, Cristobal, 1912; 8; 1390; 126; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Interior, fire engine house, Cristobal, 1912; 9; 1391; 127; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - House on Third Avenue, Cristobal, 1912; 10; 1392; 124; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Roosevelt Avenue, Cristobal, 1912; 11; 1393; 123; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Ferdinand de Lesseps’s house, Cristobal, 1912; 12; 1394; 67; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Cold storage plant, Cristobal, 1912; 13; 1395; 50; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Y.M.C.A., Cristobal, 1912; 14; 1396; 51; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Drills working and slide number one in Culebra Cut, 1912; 15; 1397; 232; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Two lower locks, materials used in constructing lock gates, Gatún, 1912; 16; 1398; 33; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Gatún Dam, near Gatún Lake, 1912; 17; 1399; 27; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Looking down over top of Gatún Locks from light house, 1912; 18; 1400; 32; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Gatún Dam from center wall of Gatún locks, 1912; 19; 1401; 47; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Light house in upper lock at Gatún, 1912; 20; 1402; 35; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Middle and lower locks and alternative entrance, Gatún, 1912; 21; 1403; 34; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Upper gates in upper Gatún lock, 1912; 22; 1404; 10; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Spillway, Gatún Dam (looking toward Gatún Lake), 1912; 23; 1405; 17; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Colonel Goethal’s private automobile, 1912; 24; 1406; 49; 5x7 (Box 1221)
  - Colonel Goethal’s private automobile, 1912; 25; 1406A; 49; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Looking over spillway toward Gatún Dam, 1912; 26; 1407; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Atlantic end of canal, French and American canal looking toward Colón[?], 1912; 27; 1408; 5; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Gatún station, Panama Railroad, 1912; 28; 1409; 6; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Looking into forebay and upper (protective) gates at Gatún (gates seven feet thick), 1912; 29; 1410; 7; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - At end of canal looking toward Gatún showing French and American canal, 1912; 30; 1411; 16; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Two lower locks toward Atlantic, Gatún, 1912; 31; 1412; 28; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Middle lock chamber, Gatún, showing curve in wall at change of lock levels, Atlantic entrance in distance, 1912; 32; 1412; 11; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  - Intermediate gate, upper lock, Gatún, Frank R. Roberson in foreground (height of gate approximately 79 feet), 1912; 33; 1414; 9; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1221)
  Box 1222
- Panama, 2.1.1.1.18
  - Spraying oil to prevent breeding of mosquitoes, Gatún (Chas Barrett, Paraíso, Rieliand Hamillan[?], San Pablo), 1912; 1; 1415; 114; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Entrance to Gatún Locks, showing lake and center wall, Pacific entrance to locks, Gatún, 1912; 2; 1416; 188; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Pacific entrance to Gatún Locks, from P.P.P. tracks, 1912; 3; 1417; 189; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Atlantic entrance to canal, 1912; 4; 1418; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Dredge at work, Atlantic end of Gatún Locks, 1912; 5; 1419; 4; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Gatún dam and lake, 1912; 6; 1420; 19; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Colonel Goethal’s private automobile at Gatún, 1912; 7; 1421; 50; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Gatún Dam at lake end of the Gatún Locks, 1912; 8; 1422; 20; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Gatún dam and lake, 1912; 9; 1423; 44; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Lake, Gatún, 1912; 10; 1424; 30; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Back of spillway, Gatún, 1912; 11; 1425; 25; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Looking down over top of locks at Gatún from light house on center wall, 1912; 12; 1426; 48; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Dam of Gatún and lake from railroad tracks, 1912; 13; 1427; 46; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - From lighthouse on lock of Gatún, looking out over the extending wall and lake, Frank R. Roberson on tracks, 1912; 14; 1428; 45; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Top of locks showing construction work, Gatún, 1912; 15; 1429; 42; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Gates for emergency dam, Gatún, 1912; 16; 1430; 37; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Detail of tower gate, upper lock, Gatún, 1912; 17; 1431; 36; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Street scene, Gatún, 1912; 18; 1432; 29; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Showing how water is released from lake by the chambers in dam from the spillway, 1912; 19; 1433; 24; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Empty spillway, overflow of dam in rear, Gatún, 1912; 20; 1434; 22; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - At the base of spillway dam, Frank R. Roberson in foreground, Gatún, 1912; 21; 1435; 23; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Colonel Sieber (or Siebert) in automobile at Gatún locks, 1912; 22; 1436; 21; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - At the base of the spillway dam, 1912 September; 23; 1437; 18; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Spillway, Gatún Dam looking down on baffle piers, 1912 September; 24; 1438; 12; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Main culvert in center wall, upper Gatún lock, 1912 September; 25; 1439; 8; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Colonel Sieber (or Siebert) and Frank R. Roberson in the Colonel’s automobile at Gatún, 1912 September; 26; 1440; 3; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Digging 66 feet below sea level at Gatún, 1912 September; 27; 1441; 2; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - 400 foot chamber of upper lock, Frank R. Roberson in foreground, looking up, Gatún, 1912; 28; 1442; 1; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Churn drills at work in Culebra Cut, 1912; 29; 1443; 53; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Old French engine and pump near Gambosa[?] slide, Culebra cut, 1912; 30; 1444; 228; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Entrance to Culebra Cut from Empire, 1912; 31; 1445; 235; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Gold Hill, Culebra Cut, 1912; 32; 1446; 86; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  - Churn drills at work, Culebra Cut, 1912; 33; 1447; 192; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1222)
  Box 1223
- Panama, 2.1.1.1.18
  - Culebra Cut, general view near Empire, 1912; 1; 1448; 85; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Culebra Cut, contractor’s hill on right, 1912; 2; 1449; 234; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Looking toward the Big Cut, tower of Culebra on hillside, 1912; 3; 1450; 236; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Crew of observation train, Culebra, 1912; 4; 1451; 63; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Cross section of lock wall, made from map, 1912; 5; 1452; 66; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - The greatest height[?] in cut, Culebra Cut, 1912; 6; 1453; 182; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Culebra Cut, showing the hill[?] on both sides of canal, 1912; 7; 1454; 183; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Culebra Cut showing big slide and drills from a distance, 1912; 8; 1455; 193; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Culebra Cut near Matachin, 1912; 9; 1456; 194; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Culebra Cut near Matachin, 1912; 10; 1456A; 194; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - By Gambosa[?] slide, Culebra Cut, showing overturned cars which were caught, 1912; 11; 1457; 226; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Big Gambosa[?] slide, Culebra Cut, showing size of rocks, 1912; 12; 1458; 227; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Hand drills along the wall of Culebra Cut, 1912; 13; 1459; 229; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Street scene, Culebra, 1912; 14; 1460; 65; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Street scene, view from Culebra railroad station, Culebra, 1912; 15; 1461; 64; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Churn drill in Culebra Cut, 1912; 16; 1462; 59; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Gorgona railroad shops, 1912; 17; 1463; 61; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Main Street, Empire, near station, 1912; 18; 1464; 190; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Street scene, Empire, 1912; 19; 1465; 60; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Observation car at Empire, Frank R. Roberson in car, 1912 September; 20; 1466; 62; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Gates in course of construction, Pedro Miguel Locks, 1912; 21; 1469; 116; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - General view of Pacific end of Pedro Miguel locks, 1912; 22; 1470; 122; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Pedro Miguel lock gate, Frank R. Roberson in foreground, 1912; 23; 1471; 120; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Frank R. Roberson in opening in Pedro Miguel lock gate, 1912; 24; 1472; 115; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Wall extending beyond the Pedro Miguel Lock, looking toward Culebra, 1912; 25; 1474; 170; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Gates in Pedro Miguel Locks, Frank R. Roberson in foreground, 1912; 26; 1475; 169; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Gate in Pedro Miguel Lock, Taken from Floor of Lock, 1912; 27; 1477; 121; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Lock and gate from top of Pedro Miguel Locks, 1912; 28; 1478; 96; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Top of Pedro Miguel Locks, Frank R. Roberson looking down, 1912; 29; 1479; 94; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Pedro Miguel Locks, construction work at Pacific end of locks, 1912; 30; 1480; 92; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Pedro Miguel Locks, taken from bridge across lock, looking into lock, 1912; 31; 1482; 89; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Frank R. Roberson on top of Pedro Miguel Locks, 1912; 32; 1483; 110; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  - Model locks, designed to show machinery in case of accident (model only), 1912 September; 33; 1484; 81; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1223)
  Box 1224
- Panama, 2.1.1.1.18
  - Administration building, Culebra, 1912 September; 1; 1485; 82; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Looking toward Empire from Culebra, 1912 September; 2; 1487; 87; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Culebra Cut, from Y.M.C.A. building, at Culebra, 1912; 3; 1489; 84; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Freight cars caught in lower Gambosa[?] slide, Culebra Cut, 1912; 4; 1490; 230; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Middle slide in Culebra Cut and steam shovel at work, 1912; 5; 1492; 231; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Churn drills and slide number one building in Culebra Cut, 1912; 6; 1493; 233; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Observation car in Culebra Cut, 1912; 7; 1494; 52; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Outlet of central chamber, Pedro Miguel Lock, Frank R. Roberson in foreground, 1912; 8; 1497; 164; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Lower end of Pedro Miguel Locks, looking toward Miraflores, 1912; 9; 1500; 93; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Pedro Miguel Locks, showing tracks for engines which tow the boats through, 1912; 10; 1502; 90; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Arches and water chamber opening in Pedro Miguel Locks, 1912; 11; 1504; 119; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Lock construction in progress, Miraflores, 1912; 12; 1505; 91; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Atlantic entrance, Miraflores Lock, 1912; 13; 1506; 215; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Lower end of Miraflores Locks, 1912; 14; 1507; 97; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Looking through Miraflores Locks before lock gates were placed, 1912; 15; 1508; 199; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Showing upper level and gate in course of construction, Miraflores Locks, 1912; 16; 1511; 198; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Miraflores Lock showing bottom level and Atlantic entrance gate in course of construction, 1912; 17; 1512; 204; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Cut from lock to Pacific entrance, Miraflores, 1912; 18; 1513; 178; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Looking through locks from Pacific entrance, Miraflores, 1912; 19; 1514; 179; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Lower locks, Miraflores, big cranes in east chamber looking north, 1912; 20; 1515; 185; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Miraflores, showing concrete walls and crane used to put concrete in place, 1912; 21; 1518; 209; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Miraflores, looking through both locks from the top, 1912; 22; 1519; 214; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Miraflores from entrance gate in lower lock, looking through both locks to upper gate, 2000 feet, 1912; 23; 1520; 223; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Miraflores, upper lock looking toward Atlantic entrance, 1912; 24; 1521; 221; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Miraflores Locks, from top of upper lock showing extension all and Pedro Miguel Lock in distance, 1912; 25; 1522; 201; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Miraflores Locks from Atlantic entrance, 1912; 26; 1523; 202; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Dr. [Colonel] Gorgas and Frank R. Roberson, close view, 1912; 27; 1524; 162; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - View from top of administration building, Ancón, 1912; 28; 1525; 218; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Dr. [Colonel] Gorgas on porch of his home, 1912; 29; 1527; 160; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Tivoli Hotel, Ancón, 1912; 30; 1528; 220; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Spillway channel, Gatún, 1912; 31; 1529; 13; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Baffle piers and dam, spillway from top, Gatún, 1912 September; 32; 1530; 14; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Crowd of workers at Miraflores waiting for train, 33; 1531; 125; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Rear of train out of Colón, Frank R. Roberson sitting, 1912; 34; 1532; 53; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Drills in Culebra Cut, 1912; 35; 1533; 54; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Observation car at Empire, Frank R. Roberson seated at left, 1912 September; 36; 1534; 88; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  - Miraflores, showing lock walls in course of construction, 1912; 37; 1535; 98; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1224)
  Box 1225
- Panama, 2.1.1.1.18
  - Third Avenue, Cristobal, Frank R. Roberson and two women, 1912; 1; 1537; 125; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - Deck scene, United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, 1912; 2; 1538; 156; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - Locks in process of construction showing cranes used for handling concrete, Miraflores, 1912; 3; 1542; 180; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - Culebra Cut, close, showing both sides, 1912; 4; 1543; 181; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - Culebra Cut, big slide in distance, 1912; 5; 1546; 187; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - Looking through Miraflores Lock from Atlantic entrance, 1912; 6; 1547; 205; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - Street scene, American homes, Ancón, 1912; 7; 1548; 206; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - Culebra Cut, big slide near Empire (number three slide or largest of the three), 1912; 8; 1549; 225; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - Mounted police, Ancón, 1912; 9; 1550; 224; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - Dr. [Colonel] Gorgas and Frank R. Roberson on porch of his home, 1912; 10; 1553; 163; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - Administration building, Ancón, 1912; 11; 1554; 195; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - Street scene, residential section, Ancón, 1912; 12; 1555; 196; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - Mounted police, Ancón, 1912; 13; 1556; 216; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - Home of Mr. Bishop, secretary of the Isthmian Canal Commission (I.C.C.), Ancón, 1912; 14; 1557; 217; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - West end of canal, Pacific, 1912; 15; 1559; 109; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - Panama Bay and islands, 1912; 16; 1563; 75; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - Street scene, 1912; 17; 1564; 212; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - Cathedral Park municipal building, 1912; 18; 1567; 210; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - Wreck of “Newport” at La Boca, 1912; 19; 1574; 108; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - Street scene in Toboga, 1912; 20; 1580; 175; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - Panama police, mounted and foot, 1912; 21; 1583; 241; 4x5 (Box 1225)
  - Selling lottery ticket, circa 1912; 22; 1584; 233; 4x5 (Box 1225)
  - Natives cooking[?] stand, circa 1912; 23; 1585; 239; 4x5 (Box 1225)
  - Natives cooking[?] stand, circa 1912; 24; 1585A; 240; 4x5 (Box 1225)
  - Group of natives, circa 1912; 25; 1586; 238; 4x5 (Box 1225)
  - Native woman selling lottery tickets, circa 1912; 26; 1587; 237; 4x5 (Box 1225)
  - Native woman selling lottery tickets, waiting on the next buyer, circa 1912; 27; 1588; 242; 4x5 (Box 1225)
  - Men studying lottery tickets, circa 1912; 28; 1589; 235; 4x5 (Box 1225)
  - American buying a lottery ticket, circa 1912; 29; 1590; 234; 4x5 (Box 1225)
  - American buying a lottery ticket, circa 1912; 30; 1590A; 4x5 (Box 1225)
  - Native and her stand of sweets, circa 1912; 31; 1591; 236; 4x5 (Box 1225)
  - Man with bananas on head, 1912; 32; 1592; 243; 4x5 film (Box 1225)
  - Two ships, taken on board the United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, 1912; 33; 1592; 244; 4x5 film (Box 1225)
  - Ship, taken on board the United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, 1912; 34; 1592; 245; 4x5 film (Box 1225)
  - Three men in tiny boat (made on board the United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo), 1912; 35; 1592; 246; 4x5 film (Box 1225)
  - Men in tiny boat (made on board the United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo), 1912; 36; 1592; 247; 4x5 film (Box 1225)
  - Men in small boat (made on board the United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo), 1912; 37; 1592; 248; 4x5 film (Box 1225)
  - Frank R. Roberson and woman on board the United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, 1912; 38; 1592; 249; 4x5 film (Box 1225)
  - Frank R. Roberson and two women on board the United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, 1912; 39; 1592; 250; 4x5 film (Box 1225)
  - Frank R. Roberson and two women on board United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, 1912; 40; 1592; 251; 4x5 film (Box 1225)
  - Frank R. Roberson and woman on board the United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, 1912; 41; 1592; 252; 4x5 film (Box 1225)
  - Two women on board the United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, 1912; 42; 1592; 253; 4x5 film (Box 1225)
  - Ship (made on board the United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo), 1912; 43; 1592; 4x5 film (Box 1225)
  - Model of Pedro Miguel Locks (copy), 1912; 44; 1594; 5x7 (Box 1225)
  - Plan showing height of locks (copy for Panama lecture 1912 September 25), 45; 1595; 5x7 (Box 1225)
  - Map of Panama Canal, 1912; 46; 1596; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - Map, profile of Panama Canal, 1912; 47; 1597; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  - Gatún Dam, spillway and locks (copy), 1912; 48; 0008; 5x7 (Box 1225)
  - Churn Drill at work in cut, Culebra, 1912; 49; 1598; 55; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1225)
  Box 1226
- Panama, 2.1.1.1.18
  - Looking aft from bridge of United Fruit Company S.S. Tenadores, 1913 September 7-9; 1; 1599; 109; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Captain Porter of the United Fruit Company S.S. Tenadores, 1913 September 7-9; 2; 1600; 107; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Deck of the United Fruit Company S.S. Tenadores, people sitting on deck chairs, 1913 September 7-9; 3; 1601; 99; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - United Fruit Company S.S. Tenadores, suite of rooms, 1913 September 7-9; 4; 1602; 103; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Main companionway and stair case, United Fruit Company S.S. Tenadores, 1913 September 7-9; 5; 1604; 100; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Group on deck of United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, 1913 September 7-9; 6; 1605; 1; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Group of officers, United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, 1913 September 7-9; 7; 1606; 3; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Captain Smith in his cabin, United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, 1913 September 7-9; 8; 1608; 6?; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Deck scene, United Fruit Company S.S. Tenadores, 1913 September 7-9; 9; 1610; 98; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Dining saloon, United Fruit Company S.S. Tenadores, 1913 September 7-9; 10; 1611; 104; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Bedroom suite on the United Fruit Company S.S. Tenadores, 1913 September 7-9; 11; 1612; 111; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Hook for slip ropes, middle lock, Gatún, 1913; 12; 1614; 49; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Looking down on upper lock, Gatún, 1913; 13; 1615; 83; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Reading room, United Fruit Company S.S. Tenadores, 1913 September 7-9; 14; 1617; 102; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Outdoor café, palm gardens, United Fruit Company S.S. Tenadores, 1913 September 7-9; 15; 1618; 105; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Smoking room, United Fruit Company S.S. Tenadores, 1913 September 7-9; 16; 1619; 110; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Man on bridge of United Fruit Company S.S. Tenadores, 1913 September 7-9; 17; 1620; 108; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Titchfield Hotel, front view, Port Antonio, Jamaica, 1913 September 7-9; 18; 1621; 8; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Steps on the water side of the Titchfield Hotel, Port Antonio, Jamaica, 1913 September 7-9; 19; 1623; 10; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Rear of Titchfield Hotel from island, Port Antonio, Jamaica, 1913 September 7-9; 20; 1624; 11; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - View from rear of Titchfield Hotel, man in foreground, Port Antonio Jamaica, 1913 September 7-9; 21; 1626; 13; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Road scene, looking toward ocean, Jamaica, 1913 September 7-9; 22; 1629; 16; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Sea promenade at Washington Hotel, Colón, 1913 September 7-9; 23; 1634; 21; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Washington Hotel at Colón, detail of front, 1913 September 7-9; 24; 1635; 22; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Looking toward the Atlantic entrance from commissary at Gatún, 1913 September; 25; 1636; 23; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - From commissary building at Gatún showing emergency dam, 1913 September; 26; 1637; 24; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Gatún Lake from commissary building, 1913 September; 27; 1638; 25; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Emergency dam at Gatún showing control tower, 1913 September; 28; 1639; 26; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Gatún Locks, taken from emergency dam, 1913; 29; 1640; 27; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Detail of emergency dam, from top, 1913 August -September; 30; 1641; 28; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Emergency dam, taken from top of Tevin[?] gate, Gatún, 1913 September; 31; 1642; 29; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Detail of gates, upper locks, Gatún, 1913; 32; 1643; 30; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Detail on top of emergency dam, Frank R. Roberson standing by chain, Gatún, 1913 September 7-9; 33; 1644; 31; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - General view of Gatún Locks looking toward the Atlantic Ocean, 1913 September; 34; 1645; 32; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  - Lights and top guard gate, Gatún, 1913 September 7-9; 35; 1646; 34; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1226)
  Box 1227
- Panama, 2.1.1.1.18
  - Upper lock showing chain safety device, Gatún, 1913 September; 1; 1647; 35; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Quadrant on Mich[?] emergency dam swings, Gatún, 1913 September 7-9; 2; 1648; 36; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Plates Mich[?] drop down at emergency dam, Frank R. Roberson in distance, Gatún, 1913 September 7-9; 3; 1649; 37; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Upper gate and emergency dam at Gatún, 1913 September 7-9; 4; 1650; 38; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Edge of gates, upper lock, Gatún, 1913 September 7-9; 5; 1651; 39; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)
  - Showing two lower locks at Gatún, 1913 September; 6; 1652; 40; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1227)